And now I am joined by the newest member
of the New York Football Giants,
linebacker and edge player, Arval Reese,
out of Ohio State. Arll,
congratulations. Welcome to the Giants.
How you feeling, man?
>> I'm feeling blessed right now. I'm
excited right now, man. I can't wait to
get out there.
>> All right,
>> I'm excited right now.
>> Yeah, no, no question about it. Giants
are excited to have you here. What are
you most excited about joining the New
York Football Giants?
>> I'm really most excited about getting to
work. Honestly, the guys I met there, I
love them. Coach Bush, Coach Dinard, sat
down with Coach Harbaugh. I loved them.
Honestly, I loved them. I can't wait to
get to work with them.
>> What was it about you talking with them
and your relationship throughout this
process that makes you so excited for
playing for that group of men?
>> Well, yeah. I sat down at dinner with
Coach Dard, Coach Bush, and the advice I
was getting from him, how and how how
much I could relate to them and how real
they were with me. That's what I felt
the most from them. That's why I'm
excited to work with them. Now, in
college, you played both offball
linebacker and you played edge. I know
at the combine usually you think of
yourself as an edge player, but how
comfortable are you just reprising that
same role you had at Ohio State? When
they need you off ball, you go there.
When they need you rushing the passer at
edge or setting the edge in the run
game, you can play there.
>> I'm I'm very comfortable with that.
That's what I do best. I'm very
comfortable with that role.
>> Now, you played for an NFL defensive
coordinator, Matt Patricia, at Ohio
State. What are some of the things that
he taught you and he had you do in his
defensive system that you think will
have you prepared to step onto an NFL
field right away?
>> Um, I think Coach Patricia helped and
was a major role in the way and he
helped me. He helped how I use my hands.
I say that Coach Patricia the strikes I
was doing, my hand placement, that all
was from Coach Patricia. Coach Patricia
came in and taught me that.
Now, talking to a couple of college
coaches around the league, I've heard
them heard them say talk about how you
played that kind of adjuster position
for Matt Patricia, which in that Bill
Bich tree requires a lot of adjustments.
Being a really smart football player,
how did that part of your game develop
over your last two years as your playing
time increased?
>> Um, yeah, when Coach P came in, he
introduced that role to me. And right
when he introduced me to that role, you
know, it was on me to it was on me to
learn both. I had to learn on the ball,
off the ball. He showed me a guy named
Jamie Collins that he coached back in
the day that he said I was that that's
how I was going to be used like. So
yeah, you know, it was on me. I had to
take on that role, didn't back down from
it.
>> You're going to be joining a very
talented defense. Brian Burns, Abdul
Carter, Kavon Tibido, Tmaine Edmonds
will will be a linebacker with you. How
excited are you to kind of get on the
field with these guys and mesh your
talents with theirs?
>> I'm very excited for that. Just playing
alongside those guys, we just think
that's so crazy. Even imagine it. I'm
very excited for it.
>> Now, how much are you familiar with the
Giants defense tradition? They have a
really big tradition of guys that play
just like you, whether it's Carl Banks,
Lawrence Taylor, offball linebackers,
edge players. How excited are you to try
to lend to that tradition and become a
part of it moving forward?
>> I'm very excited for it. Like you said,
Giants got a rich history, especially on
the defensive side. Lawrence Taylor, I
always knew about him growing up. So,
yeah, I'm excited to take on this role.
>> Arro, we can't wait to have you up here.
Thanks so much for the time and enjoy
the rest of your night. Welcome to the
Giants.
>> Yes, sir. Thanks for having me. Thank
you.
>> [music]